= kisskh.asia =
(Blossom Through the Cloud)
(Adapted from the novel on JJWXC, "Landing on My Heart", by Qiao Yao)
Be careful!
Mom, the other kids all say...
that you're the best.
How so?
Because you never scold me,
and you never hit me.
Even if I don't do well on exams,
you don't get mad.
I still hope you do well.
Please try to get a better grade next time, okay?
We'll talk about that when the next exam comes.
When is the next time?
The next time after the next time!
You little rascal.
I'm going to catch you!
(Episode 11: Happy Birthday x 3)
Come in, Xiao Ruan.
Welcome. It's your first time here, right?
Come this way.
Welcome to Hengshi's executive floor.
This is where Mr. Fu and the rest of us work.
Come, let's walk further in. I'll show you around.
This is the pantry.
Usually, people come here to have coffee and take a break.
The staff working here...
are all from the President's Office.
And this is Mr. Fu's office.
Didn't check your phone?
No. What's wrong?
I have another meeting.
Wait a moment.
Here, Xiao Ruan.
Have some water.
Mr. Fu, everyone is here.
When it's over, I'll take you to dinner.
Wait a minute.
Why should I wait just because you said so?
And taking me to dinner?
Do I not have a mouth to feed myself...
or legs to walk away?
Besides,
are you and I on good enough terms to eat together?
It's probably not about work.
(WeChat, Fu Ming Yu)
(Fu Ming Yu: I'm back.)
He can just come back.
Why notify me?
This time, Mr. Fu...
really earned some major points.
If he hadn't been there,
you would've been in trouble today.
Yeah.
A hero saving the damsel.
I think he has a chance.
Even an unreliable guy like him...
can have such a considerate side.
Sorry for the trouble, everyone.
This Fu Ming Yu...
just came back from Ma'ao...
with another woman,
and now he's rushing to ask me out.
Ms. Ruan,
where are you going?
Home.
Tell Mr. Fu...
to eat by himself.
Where is she?
Where is Ruan Si Xian?
Ms. Ruan said...
she had something to do and went home.
Did she say what it was?
She just said...
you should eat by yourself.
Hello, "Captain" Ruan.
West Chamber Banquet is at your service.
You...
You all...
Who told you to come?
I didn't order any service.
- This... - Hello.
- You... - Mr. Fu arranged this for you.
It's an in-home cooking service.
Let's hurry up and get to work.
I... Wait!
- What are you doing? - Didn't we agree?
We would have dinner together after I got off work.
Aren't you going to invite me in?
An An.
Are you busy?
I'm...
organizing photos.
What's up? Let's have some fruit and chat.
About what? I'm really busy right now.
All right. I'll let you get back to it.
Well,
I'll get going.
Mom.
Let's chat, come on.
So how was it?
Did you have fun in Ma'ao?
Seven days.
I was in Ma'ao for seven whole days.
He didn't even have time to have a single meal with me.
I don't believe he was really that busy.
I feel like taking me to Ma'ao...
was just another task on his to-do list.
Maybe he really was busy.
Look at your dad.
He's always so busy that he's constantly on the go.
Anyway, I'm pretty annoyed.
However,
the trip wasn't a total waste.
I'm absolutely certain of one thing now.
I, Zheng You An,
do not like Fu Ming Yu.
If you want to know to what extent,
it's that I 100 percent do not like him.
Help me talk to Dad too.
Tell him to give up on that idea.
What are you laughing at?
Then why did you follow Fu Ming Yu around...
all the time when you were little?
I was just a kid then.
What did I know?
It's all because of you adults.
You teased me about it every day.
You made me believe that I really liked him.
I've been mistaken for so many years.
But this time in Ma'ao,
I finally set things straight...
and found out the truth.
All right, now that you know the truth,
are you happy?
The two artists...
are obsessed with art again.
Even if you're obsessed with art,
you should still have a meal with me.
That's right.
In this big world,
eating is the most important thing.
Right. I'll answer your question while I'm at it.
I feel refreshed now.
I'm in a great mood.
What has gotten into her?
As I said before,
the most important thing is for our child to be happy.
Old Zheng.
What did you make?
Sweet and sour pork ribs.
- Go on. - Let's go.
- Let's eat. - Let's go.
- Enjoy your meal. - Enjoy your meal.
Mr. Fu, we'll get going now.
Okay, thank you for your hard work.
You're welcome.
Please.
How extravagant.
Even though you own this place,
you can't be so overbearing and unscrupulous.
You don't like it?
If you don't like it, we can eat out next time.
Is that the point?
Who wants to eat out with you?
What I'm saying is,
you just came back from Ma'ao with your girlfriend.
Why are you asking me out to a meal now?
She's not my girlfriend.
Who would believe that?
She's the daughter of the chairman of a company I work with.
She had work in Ma'ao,
but since she couldn't find a suitable flight,
she hitched a ride on my plane.
Please have a seat.
How did you know I like Sichuan and Hunan cuisine?
It's not hard to deduce the preferences...
of someone who eats spicy food...
while having a stomachache.
Try it.
Aren't you eating?
You first.
It's actually quite good.
You clearly can't handle spicy food.
- So... - So...
(Zheng You An)
What were you going to say just now?
What do you think of Zheng You An?
If Zheng You An hadn't made that call...
what would you have asked?
If she hadn't called,
that's exactly what I wanted to ask.
Fine.
Then I'll explain it one more time.
She's the daughter of the chairman of a company I work with.
Her parents and mine...
are on good terms,
so we see each other often.
That's all there is to it.
Then what kind of person is she?
She and I...
basically grew up together.
Later, she went to study abroad.
We rarely met after she left.
In the past five years,
we've seen each other no more than five times.
We haven't even spoken 20 sentences to each other.
As for what kind of person she is now, I'm not sure.
But...
I have no relationship with her.
Fine.
Forget it if you don't know.
I'm so sorry.
My car broke down on the way.
I had to push it here.
And I was at the security office registering for ages.
I'm sorry I'm late.
It's okay.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's hot out. Have some water.
- It's fine. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Did you order takeout?
You were quite nice to the delivery guy just now.
If you were a delivery guy,
I'd be nice to you too.
I can't help it.
I sympathize with the working class.
These dishes...
taste pretty good.
No rush.
You can eat more.
I have a meeting later,
so I have to head back to the office.
Xuan.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm just a little tired.
Are you flying these next few days?
Perfect. Try our new cocktail.
Sunset Boulevard.
You're the first one to try it.
- How is it? - It's sweet.
Don't underestimate it though.
It's just as strong as a Long Island Iced Tea.
Is something on your mind?
No.
Excuse me. Can I see the menu?
Coming!
Wait for me in the courtyard.
I'll be right there.
You drank the whole thing?
Are you fine?
I'm okay.
It's just like juice.
Tell me the truth.
Did your mother come to see you again?
No.
That's good.
Then let's toast.
Are you hungry?
I'm not hungry.
I think I'm a little hungry.
I wonder what your dad is cooking for us.
Be careful.
Watch where you're walking.
There's a bug there. I'm scared.
Don't be scared.
Mom is here.
Why were you drinking?
I'm in a bad mood.
What's wrong?
I'm just...
in a bad mood.
Still angry?
So you're angry,
and that's why you haven't replied to my messages.
I just didn't want to reply.
It's my fault.
I was on a business trip for so long,
and I didn't even send you a single message.
I don't care if you text or not.
Do you hate me that much?
I'm not that bad, am I?
Not really.
Actually,
you're quite nice sometimes.
- I... - But...
Sometimes,
I really want to kick you...
all the way to Trisolaris.
Why are you so angry?
Is it because of Zheng You An?
If that's the case,
I won't go out with her alone next time.
Okay?
If I'm mad at Zheng You An,
what does that have to do with you?
You're so jealous.
How can it not be about me?
You don't think...
I'm jealous of Zheng You An...
because of you, do you?
You...
Were you a hot air balloon in your past life?
Because your ego is so inflated.
Who's jealous of you?
I don't want to walk anymore.
I have an inflated ego?
Who are you looking for?
Where's Ruan Ruan?
She left.
Why are you here today instead of going to see Lu Ming?
Him?
He went out to have fun.
Perfect.
I think while Ruan Ruan isn't here,
we should discuss how to celebrate her birthday this year.
But doesn't she skip her birthday?
That's just an excuse she uses.
Because every year on her birthday,
her mother comes to see her.
She says she wants nothing to do with her mother.
But look at her. Does she look like she doesn't care?
How about this?
Let's take her out this year.
If she doesn't see her mother,
maybe she'll have a happy birthday.
Then...
let's get a cake and flowers.
How about camping by the sea?
It's a plan!
- Okay. - Then...
I'll get the cake.
I'll get the flowers.
What about me?
You?
Just stay out of the way.
I need your fingerprint.
Careful.
Are you still in a bad mood?
I am unhappy,
but it's none of your business.
Do you understand?
Don't flatter yourself.
It's not because of me.
Why did you drink so much?
It's my mouth.
So what if I drink?
Is it any of your business?
Are you my boyfriend...
or my husband?
How ridiculous.
I'm just so jealous of Zheng You An.
I'm so jealous of her.
Jealous of what?
They aren't even related by blood,
but they can be together every day.
What are you talking about?
I'm her own,
but she doesn't want me anymore.
Who doesn't want you?
My mom.
My mom abandoned me.
Why haven't you left yet?
You're drunk.
I brought you home.
You opened the door yourself.
Just because the door was open,
you let yourself in?
Banks have their doors open too.
Why don't you go rob one?
Ruan Si Xian, can't you talk to me nicely?
Are you leaving or not?
What if I don't?
If you don't leave,
I'll send you...
down in a free fall.
You don't even need the elevator.
- Hello? - Hello?
This is Fu Ming Yu.
Hello.
Hello. Is Ruan Si Xian there?
She's drunk.
I've brought her home.
Okay.
I just wanted to confirm she's home safe.
Okay, thank you.
Wait, was that...
Fu Ming Yu?
It was Fu Ming Yu.
- They... - Anyway, Ruan Ruan is drunk.
So they...
And...
Fu Ming Yu is at Ruan Ruan's place now.
No way!
- No! - It must be like that.
It must be. That's it.
I really want to call her again.
- No, you can't. - Don't disturb them.
Ruan Ruan...
She has finally found love!
Let go of me.
If you want to sleep, go to your bed.
Don't squeeze onto that small sofa.
I'm her own daughter.
But she didn't want me anymore.
It's 11pm.
Are you going back to Huguang?
Look into Ms. Dong's past.
Yes, sir.
- Mom. - Son, you're back.
Son,
I'm unhappy today.
What's wrong?
Tell me, how can there be such a person?
At tonight's private auction,
everyone knew I was there...
for Master Yue Sanlin's painting.
I even brought the money.
But when I got there,
the master's painting wasn't even among the auction items.
- Do you know what happened? - What happened?
(Bai Yang: Mr. Fu, I've found out.)
Dong Xian pulled a fast one.
She had bought the painting beforehand!
How awful.
Mom, just buy another one.
- I'll... - I'm going to make a call.
You don't want to hear me nag.
You don't want to hear me complain.
Making roast pork is better than raising a son.
Collecting treasure is better than raising a son.
Hello, Mr. Fu.
- Get straight to the point. - Here's the story.
Mr. Zheng and the current Mrs. Zheng are in their second marriage.
Everyone knows this.
Mr. Zheng's first wife passed away from illness...
shortly after giving birth to Ms. Zheng.
The current Mrs. Zheng...
had a former husband,
but he passed away a long time ago.
Get to the point.
The point is,
Mrs. Zheng had a daughter before.
It's Ruan Si Xian.
I see.
It's great that you could come.
What do you think of Zheng You An?
If Zheng You An hadn't called, what would you have asked?
If she hadn't called,
that's what I would've asked too.
I'm her own,
yet she didn't want me anymore.
I really was reading too much into things.
Careful.
Who is it?
Hello. Here's your delivery. Enjoy.
(Fu Ming Yu)
I received the breakfast. Thank you.
(Bian Xuan)
Are you awake? I was afraid you would feel unwell if you overslept.
I ordered breakfast for you.
Remember to eat it.
It wasn't from him?
(Fu Ming Yu, Recall Message)
(Ruan Si Xian: I received the breakfast. Thank you.)
(The other user recalled a message.)
It wasn't me.
Don't overthink it.
I just sent it to the wrong person.
Sorry.
"Oh"?
Thanks to my besties for breakfast.
Love you all.
Kisses.
I don't believe you.
(Thanks to my besties for breakfast. Love you all. Kisses.)
(You're here to see me again. Admit it. You like me.)
You're here to see me again.
Admit it.
You like me.
(Employee Registration Form, Ruan Si Xian)
(Birthdate: August 25, 1993)
Bai Yang.
Tomorrow, order a birthday cake for me.
Got it. Don't worry.
Make it a nice one.
Will do.
Hello, everyone.
Welcome to FM 93.7,
Jiangcheng Sound of Music.
Next, we'll bring you...
today's weather forecast...
and meteorological information.
There will be heavy rain in the city today.
The high will be 28°C,
and the low will be 15°C.
Please bring your rain gear.
The sun is so bright.
It doesn't look like it's going to rain at all.
The weather forecast these days...
is getting more and more unreliable.
Are these three orders duplicates?
What do you mean?
They all ordered the same cake.
(Customer: Si Xiao Zhen, Item: Kids' Airplane Cream Cake)
They're not duplicates.
The three buyers are all different.
The first two messages are also different.
They both wish "Happy Birthday".
The third one wrote a whole letter.
But it's obvious...
they're all for the same person.
Ruan Si Xian, Captain Ruan,
and Ruan Ruan.
No, I have to check.
Hello?
Hello.
This is Big Cousin Cake and Bakery.
I'm the "Big Cousin" here.
Did you order a children's airplane cake from us?
- That's right. - This is a cake for children.
Are you sure you want this one?
Yes. Could you make the little airplane look cuter?
- Thank you. - I see the note here.
No peaches.
Yes, that's right. Make sure not to add any peaches.
She's allergic to them.
Any other fruit is fine.
So the message on the cake should be,
"Ruan Si Xian, Happy Birthday".
Is that correct?
Wait a moment. Let's go with "Captain Ruan", yeah.
Change it to "Captain Ruan, Dad".
"Happy Birthday". Correct?
It's "Captain Ruan, Happy Birthday".
Don't mention "Dad".
Wait a second. Maybe go with "Ruan Si Xian".
I can't make up my mind.
Using the full name feels a bit...
a bit stiff.
How about "Si Xian"?
It's warmer but still polite.
"Si Xian" is good.
It implies missing her.
- Let's go with "Si Xian". - Okay.
Please pick it up on time.
He finally decided.
- Si Xian? - Si Xian.
Please come again.
Welcome.
Hello, sir. I'm here to pick up my cake.
Could you please give me...
the last four digits of your phone number?
The last four digits are 4933.
And the cake says, "Si Xian, Happy Birthday".
"Don't Mention Dad".
Dad?
No, it's just "Si Xian, Happy Birthday".
Sir, when we spoke on the phone,
you were very clear.
"Si Xian, Happy Birthday".
"Don't Mention Dad".
No. What?
What dad? What mom?
- I just said "Si Xian". - There's no mistake.
There's absolutely no mistake.
These three cakes...
are all for Ruan Si Xian.
And the writing on the cakes...
has been confirmed one by one.
This one...
is your cake.
- This one? - "Si Xian, Happy Birthday".
"Don't Mention Dad".
It's written clearly on there.
How long will it take to change it?
Half an hour.
What's wrong with people?
Bro, the weather forecast is so accurate.
- It started raining just like that. - Why are you so free?
Whatever. They're all for Ruan Si Xian anyway.
Hurry up and change that transparent box...
to an opaque one for me, okay?
Don't let anyone see it. Hurry up.
There are no parking spots.
It's fine. I'll just park here for now.
- We'll pick it up and be right out. - Okay.
Let's go.
Whose car is this?
Why is it parked here?
Let's go.
The cake!
- What should we do? - It's okay.
- It's okay. - Oh no! Where are my keys?
The keys...
- What should we do? - This...
Try to fish them out.
- I can't reach them. - What should we do?
Look. Take that.
- Try it with that. - This?
I'll try.
Here.
A little to the left.
- Left. - Oh my gosh.
Xiao Zhen!
Your car!
It's being towed! Hurry, let's go!
You're all dressed up. Who are you meeting?
You scared me.
Why didn't you make a sound?
I'm meeting a friend.
A man or a woman?
It's none of your business.
I'm just concerned about my subordinate.
A man.
Will you be back tonight?
No.
Then do you need a ride?
Are you sure?
I'm quite curious to know...
who this friend is...
who managed to get a dinner date...
with Ms. Ruan today.
Drive.
Hello, Xiao Zhen. It's hard to get a taxi there.
I'm on my way.
What?
You're already on your way?
Well,
there has been a change of plans on our end.
How about you find a place to walk around when you arrive?
Things here won't be settled...
anytime soon.
Are you standing me up?
You could say that.
It's a bit hard to explain.
I'm really sorry.
Fine, it's okay.
I don't have a habit of celebrating my birthday anyway.
Go take care of your business first.
I'll just look around on my own.
All right, okay.
What should we do?
Is this cake still usable?
Navigation ended.
- Thank you. - What are you doing?
Go home with me.
Here.
It really is a shame.
You put so much effort into this outfit.
I'm the only one who gets to see it today.
We're not ordering takeout?
No.
What do you want to eat?
Can you make a Manchu-Han Imperial Feast?
You have quite an appetite.
And even bigger ambitions.
Longevity noodles. Do you want some?
How did you know it's my birthday today?
I've read your resume.
Does the boss...
treat every employee...
with such thoughtfulness?
I think you're asking what you already know.
If I had to make longevity noodles...
for every employee on their birthday,
would I be an executive...
or an executive chef?
(Departing Ep. 11 for Ep. 12)